

KHONSA JAHRO NABILA PUTRI WIJAYA

+62 8173-84141 | khonsawijaya@gmail.com

il. Slamet Riyadi No.129, Kartasura, Sukoharjo, Jawa tengah

jl. Bendungan Nawangan No.3, Sumbersari, Lowokwaru, Malang

I am currently pursuing a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science at Brawijaya University, maintaining a strong academic record. With experience in organizational and committee roles and customer service, I have honed skills in business communication, office administration, data processing, web design, and photo/video editing for marketing activities.

Education

Aug 2022 -

Brawijaya University - Malang, Jawa Timur

Bachelor Degree in Computer science

Experience

september 2019 - juli 2023

Waitress - RM. Ayam dan Bebek Goreng Bu Laksono - Surakarta, Jawa Tengah

Tugas dan Tanggung jawab:

- Manage orders and delivery: process orders from customers, prepare ordered items, and arrange delivery to customer addresses.
- Manage finances : record income and expenses, manage payments to suppliers, and make financial reports.
- Preparing and Arranging Products: Responsible for preparing food and beverages ordered by customers and arranging them to match the order.

Organizational Experience

2018 - 2022

Treasure - MTs PPMI Assalaam yearbook committee

- · Bookkeeping of receipts, expenses, and payments of organizational finances
- Make periodic financial statements
- · Lead and attend meetings related to financial management

Class Representative - SMAN 7 Surakarta yearbook committee

- Contribute to planning and drafting end-of-year books and conditioning class members
- Interceding between committee members and class members

2022 - 2023

Vice Deputy of Documentation and Design - DEBUG FILKOM UB

- Designing the event design according to the concept and Event theme
- Working with other divisions related to design, photo and video editing in the form of publication content on social media
- Document event activities during the event

Staff of equipment - PKKMB FILKOM 2023 and INFINITE 2022

Skills

Software: Microsoft Office, Email Administration (outlook/ mailchimp), Microsoft excel, Design Editing (figma).

Language: Indonesian Language (Native), English Language (Conversation)